tdk.com 2002-06-09

# TDK USA Corporation - Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement Version 2.1  
Last Updated August 2001**

TDK Electronics Corporation is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. We've structured our Web sites so that, in general, you can visit TDK on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. This Privacy Statement reflects both the policies of TDK.com and TDKeStore.com. 

The TDK eStore is operated by TDK Online Services Corporation, which is a wholly owned subsidiary of TDK Electronics Corporation. TDK eStore understands that online security is paramount to our customers and visitors and takes measures to safeguard and protect all information collected and received through the eStore. 

We are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and we use the information that we collect in order to facilitate the process or orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. 

Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified), it will be used to support your customer relationship with TDK. 

**Awareness**

TDK provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy, practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and from the bottom of every TDK.com Web page. 

**What we collect**

On some TDK.com pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. From time to time, we may also collect information for market research purposes. In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services (including registration), we may ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products, and more detailed contact preferences. You are at no time under any obligation to provide this information and any information collected will be used for internal marketing analysis and communications to you regarding product information and product upgrades. Data collected online may also be combined with information you provide when you register your ownership of TDK products. 

The TDK eStore also allows you to make purchases. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, contact and billing information, transaction information and credit card information. The TDK eStore will track consumer shopping habits at the aggregate level and use the information to help improve the shopping experience that you have. We do not track this information on an individual level. 

**Who we share it with**

TDK will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to any third party organizations. TDK shares the information with other corporations who are acting on behalf of TDK to facilitate the marketing and transaction processing mentioned above. 

**Cookies and Their Use**

Some parts of the TDK website and eStore may use a browser feature called "Cookies". This is to enable us to personalize your shopping experience and to make the site easier for you to use when you return to the site. 

**What are Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive when you visit certain web sites. A cookie file will usually contain information such as a user ID that the web site can use to keep track of pages that have been visited or contents of a shopping cart. The only personal information that a cookie will contain is that which you have already supplied to the web site. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other web sites. A cookie will not corrupt your hard drive or transmit a virus to your computer. 

**Choice of Contact Methods**

From time to time, if given consent, we may use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest. You will be provided with the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive any unsolicited direct marketing materials from TDK. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact. 

**Accuracy of Information**

TDK strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. If you would like to update any of the information that was provided through product registration, please send an email to customer.support@tec.tdk.com . You will be asked to provide both the old and the new information, which will then be updated in our records. Requests to remove false or inaccurate information can be submitted at any time.

We will provide you with access to your online account information on the TDK eStore via the myTDK section so that you may change or update your information at the TDK eStore. To protect your privacy and security you will be asked to identify yourself and verify your identity before being granted access to your account information.

**Children's Privacy**

TDK takes special care to protect the privacy needs of children under the age of 13 and encourages parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities and interests. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are the parent or guardian of a child that you believe has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at customer.support@tec.tdk.com so that we may delete the child's information.

TDK cannot prohibit minors from visiting this site, and must rely on parents and guardians to decide which materials are appropriate for children to view and/or purchase. 

TDK sponsors an annual Japan Trail competition. Open to seventh and eighth grade students and their teachers, the competition is coordinated by local school officials and TDK representatives. Personal data is not collected online. For more information about the competition, please visit the Japan Trail home page at: http://tdk.com/japantrail/index.html.

**Third Party Links**

Links on the TDK Web site to third party Web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the TDK site. TDK has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. Thus, TDK does not endorse or make any representations about them, or about any information, software or other products or materials found there, or about any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do so at your own risk. 

**Security**

TDK is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain effective data security, accuracy of information, and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. All transactions are protected using industry standard encryption technologies, including, but not limited to, Secure Sockets Layering (SSL). 

**Your Consent**

By using TDK.com or TDKeStore.com, you consent to our use of information as described in this Privacy Policy. We may change or add to this policy, and we encourage you to review it periodically. 

**For Further Information**

If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, you can contact us at:

TDK Electronics Corporation  
901 Franklin Avenue  
Garden City, NY 11530  
1-800-835-8273   

HOME
